const questions = [
    {
      question: "At Andrew Jacksonâ€™s funeral in 1845, why was his pet parrot removed ?",
      answers: [
        'Because the parrot was crying too loud.',
        'Because his wife thought the parrot murdered him.',
        'Because the parrot was swearing.',
        'It is illegal to have a parrrot at a funeral.'
        ],
      correctAnswer: 'Because the parrot was swearing.',
    },
    {
      question: "Why wouldn't the founding fathers wouldn't let Benjamin Franklin work on the Declaration Of Independence ?",
      answers: [
        'Because they were afraid he would slip a joke into it',
        'Becayse he was not educated',
        'He was a spy',
        'Because he was not a citizen'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Because they were afraid he would slip a joke into it',
    },
    {
      question: "What was Fidel Castro's favorite food?",
      answers: [
        'French Fries',
        'Ice Cream',
        'Candy',
        'Sushi'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Ice Cream',
    },
//     {
//       question: 'You are camping in bear country. How should you store your food?',
//       answers: [
//         'Bears are a myth. There\'s no need to worry about them',
//         'Always store your food on you person at all times.',
//         'Store your food in your tent',
//         'Always use a bear canistern or hang your food and personal hygiene items on a tree limb in a bear backpacking'
//         ],
//       correctAnswer: 'Always use a bear canistern or hang your food and personal hygiene items on a tree limb in a bear backpacking',
//     },
//     {
//       question: 'What should you never day hike without?',
//       answers: [
//         'Extra food',
//         'Hat',
//         'GPS',
//         'Cell phone'
//         ],
//       correctAnswer: 'Extra food',
//     },
//     {
//       question: 'You forgot your water filter in the backcountry. What should you do?',
//       answers: [
//         'Just drink straight from the stream',
//         'Drink your own urine',
//         'Find a water source and boil the water to neutralize it',
//         'Don\'t drink any water'
//         ],
//       correctAnswer: 'Find a water source and boil the water to neutralize it',
//     },
//     {
//       question: 'What is the safest way to cross a stream while hiking?',
//       answers: [
//       'Find flat rocks to hop across on',
//       'Look for the deepest section and cross there',
//       'Avoid acrossing where the current is strong. Look for a straight, wide, and shallow section.',
//       'Always follow the marked route no matter what'
//       ],
//       correctAnswer: 'Avoid acrossing where the current is strong. Look for a straight, wide, and shallow section.',
//     },
//     {
//       question: 'While hiking you get lost. What should you do now?',
//       answers: [
//         'Stay put and wait for someone to find you',
//         'Follow streams or rivers. They will eventually lead to roads',
//         'Take off running in one direction. you will eventually hit a trail.',
//         'Eat all of your food now to get the most energy that you can.'
//       ],
//       correctAnswer: 'Stay put and wait for someone to find you',
//     },
//     {
//       question: 'You just spotted a black bear while hiking. What should you do now?',
//       answers: [
//       'Play dead',
//       'Throw your food at the bear so that it will be distracted',
//       'Approach the bear. It might want to be friends with you!',
//       'If you spot the bear before it spots you, back away keeping your eyes on the bear and wait for it to pass before continuing on.'
//       ],
//       correctAnswer: 'If you spot the bear before it spots you, back away keeping your eyes on the bear and wait for it to pass before continuing on.',
//     },
//     {
//       question: 'What is the most dangerous animal in the wilderness?',
//       answers: [
//         'Grizzly bears',
//         'Birds',
//         'Insects',
//         'Humanbeings'
//     ],
//     correctAnswer: 'Humanbeings',
];
